New Year's Eve
Here at a diner as the year comes to an end
A literal
Hell on earth
So, you two are in the same class?
We are
What?
Are we really?
Come on,ichi, switch places with me
So then
Tell me, my dude, what's up with Yamada?
It was just four days ago
頬色に茜さす日は柔らかに
恥ずたしゃように僕らは目も開かぬまま
아니 on this topic I am biased
I have been here recently
Go ahead and walk away
Let's go with theämä
I wish I shape this way
I never cried
I never loved you
beyond one
I couldn't stand
I can't see you
僕らは目も分かぬまま
Every year, we head back up to Akita.
Cold as it is, it's warmer than usual, isn't that right, dear?
Yep.
Goodness be, my boy, you look all growed up.
He's still itty-bitty, though.
Yeah.
Sure, we might be in Akita, but nothing else has really changed.
The only problem is...
I'm stuck sharing a room with her.
What, too early to roll out the beds?
It's not that.
Oh, come on, don't give me that look!
We shared a room last year as well!
Yeah, things are just the same as last year.
Except for...
Hm?
Oh.
It's from Yamada.
Food again, of course.
Speaking of Yamada...
Akita, huh?
My parents are from the Kanto region, so I'm kinda jealous.
I wish I was able to see the snow up there.
Oh, well then, I could send a picture of the snow and all.
Oh, would you?
Promise me!
Hm.
Huh?
Where are you off to?
Walk.
It's so quiet.
Hmm...
Mmm...
Huh!
Ah!
Uh...
Kyo!
How far did he go out?
Huh?
Uh...
Kyo!
Are you okay?
Uh...
Just napping!
Like heck you were napping!
Can you stand?
Uh...
Ah!
And there you have it.
We just got here, and this is my situation already.
Why'd you walk all the way out to that dangerous cliff?
I don't know.
Got too excited, I guess.
You are so full of it.
I am pretty excited, though.
You know, as a matter of fact, I believe this is probably the first time you've ever been naughty and really hurt yourself.
I wasn't being naughty!
She's probably catching on to something with those motherly intuitions.
Oh, doesn't...
Dinner that night seemed a bit extravagant.
Yes!
Say, ah!
Cut it out!
Maybe I should take a selfie.
And send it to her.
Bet I'd get a laugh.
Huh?
A video call.
Hey, you there?
Glasses and pajamas?
You okay?
Hey, can you hear me?
And I can't even sneak one in!
Hey, w-what's this all about?
That's what I wanna know.
What happened to your arm?
Nothing.
I just took a little fall.
It, um, doesn't really hurt or anything.
You had me worried.
Although now... it seems I'll be heading straight back home tomorrow.
Yeah?
That's kind of a bummer.
You had me worried
Although now it seems I'll be heading straight back home tomorrow. Yeah, that's kind of a bummer tough luck
I hung up
She was pretty cute. That was a girl from my class
Sorry must have woke you up. Wait, that wasn't like some streamer
She was super pretty though. Yeah, well, you know we um, we all have guy friends and girlfriends. Isn't that right?
Not really. Sorry
Okay, but I don't know if we're even friends, you know
Together man, if she picks up on this
Yeah, all right hurry up and get to sleep I'm beat
She's not gonna drill me somehow that feels even worse I
Don't know what that sticker is for
Hmm
That we're friends I guess for now
I've used the word friend so little it didn't even autofill for me. That's pathetic
What is that even supposed to mean?
She wants to talk again? That was fast
Your sister asleep?
I'm out in the hall now, so it's fine
So, um, how's your arm doing?
Um, no big deal
Kinda annoying is all
Yeah?
Well, if it's not too much to ask, do you have anything to drink nearby?
Something to drink?
Mmm
Oh, yeah
Can you reach it?
Yeah, I got it
Alright, now drink it
Any windows nearby? Look outside
Outside?
Oh, I can't see the moon
Huh?
Gamada, what's this all about anyway?
Oh, nothing
Oh, nothing.
Sorry for calling so late.
It's fine. Don't sleep much lately anyway.
I have an idea. Try putting your free hand on your head, okay?
Now then, move it from top to bottom, three times in all.
You got it?
Why?
It's a trick to help you sleep.
You girls love this sort of stuff, huh?
Alright, I'll let you go. Good night.
What? Yeah, good night to you too.
So, that was quick. It was like she was remote controlling me.
And so, after all that...
Kyo! You're looking right mature all of a sudden.
He looks the same as always though.
Shut up!
I ended up heading back to Tokyo after just a day.
Better at least buy some stuff to take back.
You think three of these will do?
Yes, dear.
Yamada loves dogs, I think. Right?
Oh, wow. That's so cute. Let's get matching ones.
What? I don't think so.
Actually, let's do it.
Why are you the one acting disappointed?
If we're friends, a little gift is fine, isn't it?
And so, this girl, right? She's adorable, but she's so fickle and all over the place. You know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
So, like, girls are more than just their looks. Charm is what's key when it comes to it.
Why do I feel like she thinks I'm crushing over someone out of my league?
I mean, I am, but still.
And really, she's just like me in that way.
Always trying to give up on what she really wants before she gets hurt.
We're both that type.
But...
My head is so fixed on Yamada that I can't even spend a moment not rereading our messages.
So, hey then. That girl you were talking with yesterday?
Yamada.
Yamada?
Wait, I'm confused. Wasn't the friend who left you a note when you were sick named...
No way! That was her?!
Her handwriting was so bad, I assumed she was a boy.
Maybe you do have a chance, Kyo.
Yeah, right.
She seems awfully friendly. You should introduce us sometime.
Mom, come on, wake up!
What?!
Stop it!
Look! It's the matching keychain we bought.
Let's bring them on our temple visit.
Huh? Going somewhere?
Oh, uh, just returning some books.
Technically, that's not a lie.
Gotta bring the manga and scarf from Christmas I forgot to give back.
Also, this gift from Akita.
Ah!
Oh!
Hey!
I thought we were meeting up.
We were. But then I remembered you've got a hurt arm.
You won't be able to ride a bike like that.
Uh...
Sure, but what if you had missed me?
I guess so.
It's been a while.
Five days, actually.
Uh...
Sorry, this is Wontaro.
My dog.
Uh...
Spin around!
Now that I think about it, a non-food gift might be a bit much.
It'd probably creep her out knowing I remembered she likes dogs, too.
Some kind of snack would have been better.
This is Yamada, after all.
I've been acting without thinking a whole lot lately.
Uncharacteristically.
This is where that gets me.
Need to show some restraint.
Here.
I opened it for you.
Thank you.
Hey!
Try giving my dog a command.
Me?
N-now spin around.
Down, boy.
Uh...
Your paw.
He was just about to do it.
You think so?
Her hands are freezing.
Pretty chilly.
Yeah.
Little bit.
Oh...
Oh, yeah.
Your scarf.
Huh?
Oh!
There it is.
I put it in a bag, so it wouldn't get dirty.
Just so you know...
I was gonna let you keep it for yourself.
But...
But I...
Thought that...
You wouldn't...
Want it.
And so...
Like...
Well then...
Well what?
Um...
Just the...
From Akita.
It's a...
A...
Little souvenir.
Ah...
From Akita.
It's a...
A...
Little souvenir.
Ah!
Wow!
Hey!
Stop it!
Thank you, Ichikawa.
Ah...
Hey!
Stop it!
Thank you, Ichikawa.
Ah...
No, thank you.
I think I'll name my keychain Akita Kentaro.
You're the worst at naming things.
That's not a dog name.
By the way, so visit a temple for New Year's?
Uh...
Yeah.
I think.
With my family, though.
Really?
Sounds perfect!
I'll message you the place and time later, alright?
See ya!
What?
Uh...
Several days later...
Before I realized it, I was texting Yamada every day.
Nope!
Don't wanna be a creep and ask about other girls!
Better play it safe with this one.
After all...
I might have just let it all get to my head.
I'm freezing...
What?
For real?
I mean...
Yeah.
That's New Year's Eve for you.
You better get my drink and get out of here.
Oh!
It's the bike kid!
Huh?
Uh...
Who's he again?
Dunno.
Beats me.
Wait.
Aren't you that guy Ichi?
Um...
Ichi...
Ichihara.
That's right.
And so...
Here we are in hell.
Hey, you listening?
I asked what's Yamada up to.
I'm not dumb.
He's trying to use me.
Alright then.
You have her line?
Her line?
Oh no, I don't.
She only communicates via telepathy.
This girl over here won't tell me a thing.
But you're classmates too, right?
What?
Are we really?
Pretending not to know me, huh?
Good call.
Would only make things worse if we said we knew each other.
Wait a second.
Isn't this kid the one Yamada?
Ah!
My foot must have slipped.
Anna Yamada.
Well, it looks like you do know her line.
Way to break my heart.
Uh, no.
I just, um...
Just leave the poor kid alone, will ya?
You're probably scaring him.
Hey, huge favor.
Will you get me a coffee?
Huh?
Hmm?
Hmm.
I'm gonna go get a refill too.
Finally comes down to a use of force.
Hmm.
Uh.
Listen.
I won't tell anyone I got it from you.
And I'll also tell the girls you wouldn't give me Yamada's line.
I don't want to cause any trouble.
So, what do you say?
What do you say?
The sifties?
Hmm.
Oh.
Well nothing.
I...
Will not.
Why?
Gimme a reason.
The reason is...
I have none.
I just don't want to.
Okay, I better go.
Hey, Tihara, walk me back, okay?
What?
It's all dark and scary.
Uh, I can go with you then.
Nah, it's fine.
He and I, we're good friends now.
This is bad. I'm almost starting to like her.
Hey, nice work back there. Although you're a crappy liar.
I'm not. I just wasn't ready for that.
You should probably be straight with him next time he comes around.
He's got the wrong idea about me and Yamada.
The wrong idea?
So, we can do this then.
Never knew you could move that fast.
No, by wrong, I meant that...
I think I might possibly like Yamada.
Mm-hmm.
I know! I know! I know! I know! I know! No!
Listen, dude. It's super-duper obvious.
Uh...
This should be far enough.
Hey, uh...
Thank you.
It's no big deal.
Anyone else probably would have done the same thing.
Not that.
I mean, what I...
Hmm?
Mm-hmm.
Do you want to come inside?
Uh...
B-bye now.
Happy New Year.
Just when I was starting not to hate her!
I said out loud that I like her.
And now...
I can't help it.
Hey, Chikawa.
Hey.
W-what's going on?
It's rare for you to be calling me.
I can't help but want to hear her voice.
Oh, uh...
Right.
So, Happy New Year to you.
What?
Already?
I wanted to be the first to say it.
Hi, girls!
Hm?
Maliko's here.
What?!
Oh, sure.
Won't keep you then.
One of these days, I'll tell you.
I like you.
Huh?
I love what you've done with the trash here.
熱がここまで届いて僕は背伸びしてた大人見てる君は見て知りたいんだ君のこと近づきだって夢じゃなくて心が痛くてまた言葉にしたくて
熱がここまで届いてたくて